iimcal.ac.in 2015-03-22

# Privacy Policy - IIM Calcutta

### Privacy

#### Indian Institute of Management Calcutta (IIMC) Privacy Policy

We at IIMC value your privacy and understand how important it is for you. To that effect, we have the following privacy policy in place with regard to the collection, use and dissemination of personal information collected by this website. This document will help you understand the terms and conditions under which personal information is provided to this website. Please note that this policy is effective only within IIMC’s domain, and does not apply to websites that may be accessible from external links provided in various pages of this website. Also note that due to the very nature of internet technology and evolving threats, this policy may be updated from time to time. All such updates will be posted in the privacy policy page. In continuing to use this website, you indicate your acceptance of the terms and policies mentioned here.

#### Information Collection and Use

While you can use parts of this website without providing any personal information, certain sections will only be accessible after you have registered with the website by providing specific data. These sections include, but are not limited to Donations, Registrations, Books, Journals and Alumni Profiles. The information collected by IIMC will be used strictly for the purpose stated at the time of collection. Such information will not be sold, traded, rented or in any way given to a third party, including direct marketing companies and similar organisations for commercial purposes. However, IIMC may reveal the collected information to its employees, agents, consultants and others who the IIMC decides need to know the information. The institute may also divulge the information to third parties, including law enforcement officials, courts and others based on its discretion. 

#### System Information Including IP Addresses

Information that is not personal in nature, i.e., IP addresses, web browser and operating system details, browsing habits, demographical and geographic data and other similar information may be logged and used to analyze and extrapolate information about general user behavior within the IIMC website. Such extrapolations and statistics may be made public; however, they cannot be tracked to individual users. IP addresses are not linked to anything that can help identify the user. Neither are IP addresses, except in rare occasions, handed out third parties. 

#### Cookies

This website uses “cookies” to track usage and manage services on the website. Cookies are small bits of data that may be transferred to the user’s hard drive when he logs in or accesses a particular part of the website. These are used for a variety of purposes including authentication and can be blocked by reconfiguring the appropriate settings in your web browser. Doing so may, however, restrict access to certain parts of the website. Cookies can also be removed from the user’s hard drive whenever he wishes through his browser options. Information collected through cookies cannot be traced back to the user as it contains no personally identifiable data like name, address or phone number.

#### Online Forms

The IIMC website uses online forms where you may be asked to provide certain personal information. This is necessary to access certain services in the website (e.g. donations, registrations, books and journals) or to take part in surveys. By filling out and submitting the form you are understood to have consented to IIMC storing and using the information for the purposes for which it has been provided.

#### Security

At IIMC, we take every possible precaution to ensure that your data is safe and secure. Unfortunately, we have to control over the transmission medium and digital transmission over the internet can rarely be completely secure. Thus, we cannot ensure the safety of the information transferred to us, and you need to do so at your own risk. Once we receive the data, we will strive to keep it secure using the latest technology, constant upgrades to our digital security infrastructure and restricted access. All information you provide as will be stored in IIMC secured servers within IIMC premises. However, we make no guarantees about the security of the data in case of unforeseen circumstances.
